# LONG NGUYEN

# Full-Stack Developer

✓ longnb306@gmail.com

**L** +1 (408) 332-3876



in /azerozvn

#### **RESUME OBJECTIVE**

Once an inspired technophile, moving and setting up a new life in the U.S. surely is not an easy task. My aim now is rebuilding my focus in technology ground as soon as possible. I believe my previous experiences can play a handful role in any uprising technology firms.

#### **EDUCATION**

California State University, Sacramento 2019 - 2021 (expected)

Undergrads in Computer Science

Sacramento City College 2017 - 2019

No AS - transfer in Computer Science

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### INSPI Corp.

Front-end Developer

• Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

**#** Jun 2015 - Apr 2016

Responsible for UI/UX design and front-end development, perform testing to enhance overall user interactions and traffic by 40%

Modularize front-end components, integrate smart HTML5/CSS3 into use with AngularJS 1.x. with high reuseability that reduces production delivery time by 30%

Implement a public platform that allows users to create monitored-content on their own interests, leading to a social network trends in entertainment and knowledge exploration.

Recruit over 30 and train 3 members for core team before moving abroad.

#### AdNetSoft CO.

♣ Full-stack Developer

• Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

 **Sep 2014 - Jan 2015** 

Involve in building websites for businesses based on requests. Tasks include system architecture design, front-end and back-end development, and unit / integration testing.

Develop dynamic and interactive modules for future usage in website production, utilize web applications using cloud services, practice SEO on PHP and Wordpress-based products.

#### Freelance

Web Developer

• Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

de Oct 2013 - Aug 2014

Individually take request and deliver freelance design/website for early start-ups and entrepreneurs as well as learning new technologies

Seasonal team member for small businesses in finding digital solutions

## **ACTIVITIES**

Semi-finalist of UIT BootCamp - Summer 2014 in HCMC

Cooperator for Project: EHKOO - a developers' community blog.

Part-time graphic designer at CSE department - Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology

#### **SKILLS**

HTML5 / CSS3 / Vanilla JavaScript

MEAN / MERN Stack

Bootstrap / Semantic UI

PHP / Wordpress

Git / SVN

Agile Development

Photoshop

#### **LANGUAGES**

English: Proficient

Vietnamese: Native

Spanish: Elementary

#### **REFERENCES**

Quan Vo - CEO, INSPI Corp.

An Cao - Founder, EHKOO

Dung Chinh - Senior Dev, EdGuru